https://www.radview.com/privacy-policy/

SolutionsLoadRunner ReplacementHigher EducationWebsite Load TestingCloud Load Testing.NET Load TestingJava Load Performance TestingOracle Forms Load TestingWeb Services and APIsSeleniumContinuous Integration (CI)CRM and ERPProductTest creationTest executionPerformance analysisTechnologies supportedResourcesFrequently Asked QuestionsVideoseBooksCase StudiesDatasheetsWhitepapersBlogPricingStart TestingGet a DemoLoginStart Testing
First Name
Last Name
Job Title
Organization
Phone
Corporate Email
Country CountryUnited StatesCanadaAustraliaFranceGermanyIndiaNetherlandsSwedenSwitzerlandUnited KingdomAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoriesBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCote D'ivoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesFYROMGabonGambiaGeorgiaGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island And Mcdonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao Peoples Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and The GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited States Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican City StateVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)Wallis And Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenYugoslaviaZaireZambiaZimbabwe
StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict Of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
ProvinceAlbertaBritish ColumbiaManitobaNew BrunswickNewfoundlandNorthwest TerritoriesNova ScotiaNunavutOntarioPrince Edward IslandQuebecSaskatchewanYukon Territory
Download Purpose Download PurposeI am evaluating load testing solutionsI want a free load testing solution Please keep me informed about Radview news and offers
Thank you for downloading WebLOADCheck Your Inbox For WebLOAD! A mail is on its way to you with the download link, as well as installation instructions.Click hereif you do not receive an email. Request a Quote
First Name
Last Name
Job Title
Organization
Phone
Corporate Email
Country CountryUnited StatesCanadaAustraliaFranceGermanyIndiaNetherlandsSwedenSwitzerlandUnited KingdomAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoriesBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCote D'ivoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesFYROMGabonGambiaGeorgiaGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island And Mcdonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao Peoples Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and The GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited States Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican City StateVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)Wallis And Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenYugoslaviaZaireZambiaZimbabwe
StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict Of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
ProvinceAlbertaBritish ColumbiaManitobaNew BrunswickNewfoundlandNorthwest TerritoriesNova ScotiaNunavutOntarioPrince Edward IslandQuebecSaskatchewanYukon Territory Please keep me informed about Radview news and offers
Thanks for your interest in WebLOAD!We will get back to you shortly. Meanwhile, we invite you to learn more about performance testing on our RadView Blog Free
First Name
Last Name
Job Title
Organization
Phone
Corporate Email
Country CountryUnited StatesCanadaAustraliaFranceGermanyIndiaNetherlandsSwedenSwitzerlandUnited KingdomAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoriesBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCote D'ivoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesFYROMGabonGambiaGeorgiaGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island And Mcdonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao Peoples Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and The GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited States Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican City StateVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)Wallis And Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenYugoslaviaZaireZambiaZimbabwe
StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict Of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
ProvinceAlbertaBritish ColumbiaManitobaNew BrunswickNewfoundlandNorthwest TerritoriesNova ScotiaNunavutOntarioPrince Edward IslandQuebecSaskatchewanYukon Territory
Download Purpose Download PurposeI am evaluating load testing solutionsI want a free load testing solution Please keep me informed about Radview news and offers
Thank you for downloading WebLOADCheck Your Inbox For WebLOAD! A mail is on its way to you with the download link, as well as installation instructions.Click hereif you do not receive an email. Standard
First Name
Last Name
Job Title
Organization
Phone
Corporate Email
Country CountryUnited StatesCanadaAustraliaFranceGermanyIndiaNetherlandsSwedenSwitzerlandUnited KingdomAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoriesBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCote D'ivoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesFYROMGabonGambiaGeorgiaGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island And Mcdonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao Peoples Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and The GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited States Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican City StateVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)Wallis And Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenYugoslaviaZaireZambiaZimbabwe
StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict Of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
ProvinceAlbertaBritish ColumbiaManitobaNew BrunswickNewfoundlandNorthwest TerritoriesNova ScotiaNunavutOntarioPrince Edward IslandQuebecSaskatchewanYukon Territory Please keep me informed about Radview news and offers
Thanks for your interest in WebLOAD!We will get back to you shortly. Meanwhile, we invite you to learn more about performance testing on our RadView Blog Premium
First Name
Last Name
Job Title
Organization
Phone
Corporate Email
Country CountryUnited StatesCanadaAustraliaFranceGermanyIndiaNetherlandsSwedenSwitzerlandUnited KingdomAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoriesBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCote D'ivoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesFYROMGabonGambiaGeorgiaGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island And Mcdonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao Peoples Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and The GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited States Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican City StateVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)Wallis And Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenYugoslaviaZaireZambiaZimbabwe
StateAlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict Of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming
ProvinceAlbertaBritish ColumbiaManitobaNew BrunswickNewfoundlandNorthwest TerritoriesNova ScotiaNunavutOntarioPrince Edward IslandQuebecSaskatchewanYukon Territory Please keep me informed about Radview news and offers
Thanks for your interest in WebLOAD!We will get back to you shortly. Meanwhile, we invite you to learn more about performance testing on our RadView Blog
Privacy PolicyThis is RadView Software LTD.’s (“RadView” or “We”) online privacy policy for the radview.com website (the “Website”). This policy applies only to transactions entered into, and information gathered through the Website and related services, and does not apply to activities unrelated to the Website. By using the Website, you agree to accept the practices and terms set forth in this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”). In this Privacy Policy, we describe:Our Commitment to PrivacyThe Information We CollectHow We Collect InformationWhere We Store InformationWhat About Links to other sitesHow We Use InformationHow To Access Or Correct Your InformationHow You Can Opt-OutHow To Contact UsWhat Constitutes Acceptance of This Privacy PolicyPolicy Updates Our Commitment to PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this Privacy Policy to explain how your personally identifiable information is collected (both on-line and off-line) and used, and to explain the choices you can make about the way your information is used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available by a web link on our homepage. RadView does not sell or share the personally identifiable information it collects from you with third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy. Our privacy practices may vary as required by local law.If you would like to contact RadView without submitting personally identifiable information online, you can contact us by using the contact information provided on our web pages.The Information We CollectPersonally Identifiable Information. If you wish to contact RadView, we typically ask you to provide personally identifiable information, such as name, address, phone number, e-mail address, as well as information about the products you are using. This information helps us to reply to you. To use certain parts of this Website, you may be required to complete the registration form, a request for information, a request for a RadView White Paper, or download of an evaluation software and provide contact information (such as name and email address). If you are making a purchase on-line, we will also require your credit/debit card information, expiration date, billing address, shipping address and related information. If you refuse to provide the information that RadView requires in order for RadView to provide you with a product, service or information, you will not receive the product, service or information.Here are some details about certain features of our Site:NewslettersIf You register for a RadView newsletter, we will use Your email address to send the newsletter to You.Career InquiriesRadView accepts inquiries and applications regarding our open job postings through the Website. This may include resume files. Personal information submitted by job applicants when applying for a position and is only used for the purpose of evaluating the candidate for a position at RadView and is managed according to RadView’s human resources department policies.Investor InquiriesRadView’s investor relations department accepts requests for corporate and securities information about RadView through the Website. Personal information submitted with such requests is only used by RadView to respond to the investor’s request as long as the request is for investor information.Marketing to YouWe may use information held about you to provide you with information about products or services we feel may interest you. This may be by contacting you by phone or by email.If you do not want us to use your information in this way, you can unsubscribe from such emails using the link provided in emails, tell your RadView contact, or email us at info@radview.com.Non-Personally Identifiable and Aggregate InformationWe may use your IP address and other non-personally-identifiable information to help diagnose problems with, and administer, the Website. The non-personally identifiable information we may gather includes the type of browser that you use and IP address, the content that you access and the length of your visit to the Website. RadView uses this information, typically in aggregate form, to enhance the operation of the Website, analyze interest in the areas of the Website and to tailor content displayed to users. We may also release aggregate information about user trends to partners and other third parties. An example of this type of information would be patterns of use of the Website based on geography or industry. We also retain aggregated log files of requested content in order to report overall usage and to evaluate user trends.How We Collect InformationThere are a number of ways in which RadView may collect personal information from you. Personal information may be collected if you provide personal information via: Website registrations, Website forms, faxes, surveys, responses to mailed materials, subscription to our newsletter and other publications and contests, our interaction in telephone calls, and in person. In addition, RadView may collect aggregate information on what web pages customers access or visit.To use certain parts of this Website, you may be required to complete the registration form and provide contact information (such as name and email address). In the event that our Website allows on-line shopping, you will be required to provide your name, shipping address, credit card number, expiration date and similar information.RadView may also collect information through the use of cookies. A cookie is a small file that a website puts on a user’s hard drive. This file identifies specific information about previous visits to the site. The cookie may store the user’s country, language, an assigned random session ID, name and address information. Most browser applications allow you to block or limit the use of cookies. Consult the help menu of your browser application for details. If you block the use of cookies, you may not be able to use some of the features on the Website.Those who want to communicate with RadView but do not wish to give personally identifiable information online may use the contact information that we provide on our web pages. Where We Store Information. RadView uses commercially reasonable efforts to store and maintain personal information You submit on the Website to protect it from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction by unauthorized parties. We may store information that we collect through our Webite indefinitely except as otherwise required by law. Unfortunately, the transmission of information through the Internet is not completely secure and We cannot therefore guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our Website. We will endeavor to protect your information and prevent unauthorized access to your information once We receive your information.What About Links to Other Sites?The Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that RadView is not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites. When you leave our site, we encourage you to read the privacy policies of each website that you visit. RadView’s Privacy Policy is for the Website only.How We Use Information:RadView may share the information it collects with RadView’s affiliates, agents and partners so that RadView and its affiliates, agents and partners can:respond to your questionsprovide services, including customer supportprovide you with product news and newsletters, including information about events, seminars, updates and helpful tips regarding the products and services of RadView and its partners and affiliatesenable you to participate in contestssend you information, special promotions and commercial advertisements regarding the products and services of RadView and its partners and affiliatescontact you with surveys to help us improve the way we do businessAllow you to register with us and sign up for online services and productscreate and maintain OEM, reseller and distributor partnershipsNotify you about administrative matters relating to the Website and the products and services of RadView and its partners and affiliatesImprove the products and services of RadView and its partners and affiliates, and the way we do businessRadView’s partners include independent vendors, service providers, contractors, suppliers, licensors, licensees, contractors, distributors, resellers, dealers, OEMs and other parties who have a business relationship or a potential business relationship with RadView.When you request or order products, information or services, RadView may transfer your personally identifiable information to a RadView affiliate, agent or partner. In some instances, when RadView does this, the RadView affiliate, agent or partner may share information with an unaffiliated third party for purposes related to your request or order, such as fulfilling a request, providing or receiving information related to the request, providing or receiving a service related to the request, processing credit, obtaining export clearance and arranging for shipping and handling.While RadView cannot guarantee complete security of the information we collect from you, whenever RadView transfers personally identifiable information to RadView’s affiliates, agents and partners, it is with the understanding that the information should be used for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and that reasonable measures should be taken to aid against unauthorized access to such information.RadView may use cookies to track the number of users to our website over time, recognize repeat visits to our Website and to facilitate Web navigation and online shopping. RadView may also use cookies to track pages visited during a single session. RadView may use cookie information to adjust the presentation of our Website and to make it more effective. We may use cookies to store user preferences, record session information, record user-specific information (such as the pages the user accesses or visits), alert users to new areas that we think might be of value to them, market products and services to users and record past activity at a site. RadView may also use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Website, track user’s movements and gather broad demographic information. RadView may link the information it collects by the use of cookies to specific personally identifiable information.Some of our partners may use cookies on our site. However, we have no access to or control over those cookies.Personally identifiable information may be combined with business information. Information collected on-line may be combined with information collected off-line. Personally identifiable information may be enhanced or merged with data from third parties for the purposes of marketing. In the event of a merger, acquisition, spin-off or other transaction related to RadView, a RadView business unit or a portion of RadView’s assets, RadView may transfer the information collected from you to the surviving party, acquiring party or other party related to the transaction. When RadView believes it is required by law, RadView may also share that information with government agencies and authorities and as requested in court or administrative proceedings.RadView reserves the right to disclose the information it collects if RadView believes that such disclosure is necessary to comply with applicable law or legal process, to avoid liability for RadView and/or its affiliates, agents and partners, and/or to protect the rights and property (including intellectual property) of RadView and others, including RadView’s affiliates, agents, partners and customers. Further, RadView may disclose the information it collects if RadView suspects that an individual or entity has provided fraudulent or illegal information, has committed an illegal, fraudulent or wrongful act or omission, has attempted to pose as someone else, or has attempted an unauthorized use or access of any computer system or website.The information that RadView collects may be collected, transferred to, stored and processed in the United States and any other country in which RadView and its affiliates, agents and partners maintain facilities. By using this Website or providing your information to RadView, you consent to such transfer of your personally identifiable information. You may opt-out of such transfers by following the opt-out procedures set forth below.How You Can Access and Correct Your InformationYou can request access to correct your personally identifiable information by contacting us at the following: RadView Software Ltd. 13 Haamal St. Park Afek, Rosh Haayin 4809249 Israel Fax: +972-3-9157011Email: support at radview.comYou may correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. RadView reserves the right to verify your identity before granting access to this information or making corrections, and reserves the right to deny access to anyone who does not confirm their identity to RadView’s satisfaction.How You Can Opt-OutYou have choices about how your information is used and transferred. If you do not wish RadView to use your information to send you promotions and commercial advertisements regarding the products of RadView and its partners and affiliates, you may opt-out of such communications by contacting RadView as set forth below. If you do not wish RadView to transfer your information to RadView’s affiliates, agents and partners so that they may send you promotions and commercial advertisements, you may opt-out of such a transfer by contacting RadView as set forth below. If you do not wish to receive promotions and commercial advertisements through email or SMS messages, you may opt-out of receiving such communications by contacting RadView as set forth below. If you do not wish RadView to transfer your information to the United States or outside of your country for processing, you may opt-out by contacting RadView as set forth below.To opt-out, please identify the subject of your communication as “Remove,” specify the types of uses or transfers of your personally identifiable information that you wish to opt-out of, and contact us as follows:RadView Software Ltd. 13 Haamal St. Park Afek, Rosh Haayin 4809249 Israel Fax: +972-3-9157011Email: support at radview.comIf you opt-out, RadView reserves the right for RadView and its affiliates, agents and partners to continue to use and transfer your information in order to process and fulfill your orders and requests for service, information and products and to notify you about administrative matters relating to the Website and the products and services of RadView and its partners. Contact Us. We welcome questions or comments about our Privacy Policy. You may also contact us if you feel that your personal information is used in a way inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. You can do this by contacting us as follows:RadView Software Ltd. 13 Haamal St. Park Afek, Rosh Haayin 4809249 Israel Fax: +972-3-9157011Email: support at radview.comWhat Constitutes My Acceptance of This Privacy Policy?BY USING THE RADVIEW SERVICES AND/OR THE WEBSITE, YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION, BOTH PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE AND NON-PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE, AS DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.Policy Updates. RadView may revise its Privacy Policy from time to time. Please revisit this site on a regular basis to check for any revisions and RadView’s then-current Privacy Policy. You may opt-out of the usages specified in the then-current Privacy Policy at any time by following the opt-out procedures specified in that Privacy Policy.Date of this Last Policy Update: June, 2010.WebLOAD Free Edition50 Virtual UsersWebLOAD Free Edition includes all features + community support.
First Name* First Name is required. Last Name* Last Name is required. Job Title* Job Title is required. Company* Company is required. Phone* Phone is required. Corporate Email* Please provide a corporate e-mail address Country*
Select Country*United StatesCanadaAustraliaFranceGermanyIndiaNetherlandsSwedenSwitzerlandUnited KingdomAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoriesBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCote D'ivoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesFYROMGabonGambiaGeorgiaGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island And Mcdonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao Peoples Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and The GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited States Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican City StateVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (British)Virgin Islands (U.S.)Wallis And Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenYugoslaviaZaireZambiaZimbabwe SelectCountry is required. State*
Select State*AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict Of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyoming Select Province*
Select Province*AlbertaBritish ColumbiaManitobaNew BrunswickNewfoundlandNorthwest TerritoriesNova ScotiaNunavutOntarioPrince Edward IslandQuebecSaskatchewanYukon Territory Select Download Purpose*I am evaluating load testing solutionsI want a free load testing solution Download Purpose is required. Message
I agree to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy Please agree to the terms above * Mandatory fields
About WebLOAD  Why WebLOAD  Solutions  Company  RadView Blog © 2015-2020 Copyright RadView Software Ltd. All Rights Reserved.We use cookies to give you the best experience on our site. By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies and privacy policyACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
20
